Mason Benson

 $\label{linkedin.com/in/mason-benson-6591b5102} $$ \mbox{linkedin.com/in/mason-benson-6591b5102} $$ \mbox{Chicago, IL}$

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Web Development and IT services professional well-versed in JavaScript and node.js. Experience with network security, collaboration technologies, IoT, cloud & managed services, data center, and telecommunications. Excellent problem solving and communication skills. Exceptional interpersonal skills with ability to influence and build positive relationships among diverse individuals. Strong time management and organizational abilities. Broad based digital, software, technical knowledge and IT proficiency.

EXPERIENCE

Account Manager

LaSalle Solutions/Trace3 – Chicago, IL/ Remote | November 2020 - **Present** LaSalle Solutions acquired by Trace3 April 2022

Account manager operating as a lead point of contact for information technology teams to coordinate business operations. Responsible for analyzing various information sources to maintain data accuracy while optimizing maintenance coverage for customers. Activities include: coordinating with inside sales for the completion of all requested hardware quotes and ensuring the most efficient and cost-effective ordering and delivery process for account hardware transactions.

Retail/Business Banker

Fifth Third Bank – Lake Zurich, IL | August 2016 - 2020 American Chartered Bank acquired by MB Financial August 2016 MB Financial acquired by Fifth Third Bank May 2019

Accomplished banking sales professional with a track record of meeting aggressive sales targets related to personal loans and meeting banking sales goals. Adept at prospecting and matching priority banking products with customer needs and assisting clients in consolidating debt through priority bank products. Consistent top performer achieving top sales performance.

- Built and maintained successful relationships with retail and business customers that enabled achieving banking goals
- Maintained all legal and compliance filings to ensure company standards and policies were met
- Provided coaching and training of key staff members
- Worked with various charitable entities (i.e. Little City) management to support the community and expand opportunities for children and adults with intellectual and developmental disabilities

Customer Service-Server

College Bridging Position: Biaggi's Ristorante Italiano – Deer Park, IL | July 2015 - July 2016

Highly organized and personable customer service representative with experience providing exceptional customer experiences.

- Dedicated to ensuring customer satisfaction by remaining customer experience focused, accessible and exceeding customer needs.
- Exceptional interpersonal and team building skills with an aptitude for building rapport with a diverse range of customers, managers, and colleagues.

Intern Reporter - College Internship

WGN-TV Independent Television Station - Chicago, IL | May 2013 - August 2013

Worked closely with news anchors, field reporters, and technical support to

report information on stories and produce articles for multimedia and broadcast media. Assisted reporters in the field covering critically important media events. Conducted field interviews and learned required media support needs.

- Chosen for a coveted intern/position out of a competitive field of candidates.
- Covered multiple media stories and interviewed related personalities (i.e. Sheriff Tom Dart) to illustrate and tell relevant media stories.

Community Service Officer

Wheeling Park District - Wheeling, IL | May 2013 - August 2013

Conducted motor vehicle, bicycle, and foot patrol on Wheeling Park District property. Worked with the Wheeling Police Department to keep visitors safe and educated on park rules and policies. Assisted with resource management.

EDUCATION

Bachelors - Political Science

University Of Missouri | Columbia, MO | May 2015

- University of Missouri Men's Lacrosse Team
- Phi Kappa Psi